topg.org 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy

TOPG is owned by SPREADBEYOND LTD and is registered and approved by ANSPDCP (National Supervisory Authority for Personal Data Processing) under no. registration 32985. We have also made all required changes to be in accordance with the EU GDPR Regulations.

**Information note on personal data protection**

We collect and process the data submitted in accordance with the requirements of Law no. 677/2001 and of Law no. 506/2004. According to the requirements of Law no. 677/2001 on the Protection of Individuals with regard to the Processing of Personal Data and Free Movement of such Data, as amended and supplemented and of Law no. 506/2004 on the processing of personal data and the protection of privacy in the electronic communications sector, Spreadbeyond LTD has the obligation to administer safely and only for the specified purposes, the personal data that you provide to us, a member of the family you or another person. The purpose of data collection is: advertising, marketing and advertising; electronic communications services. You are / are not required to provide the data, which is required for advertising, marketing and advertising; electronic communications services. Your refusal makes it impossible for you to participate in our company's campaigns; the impossibility of providing electronic communications services in optimal conditions. The registered information is intended for use by the operator and can only be communicated to the following addressees: Spreadbeyond LTD (legal representatives) and the contractual partners of the company, subject to the contractual confidentiality provisions, service providers and goods, debit / recovery of debts and other participants in civil or criminal proceedings, in legal proceedings. According to Law no. 677/2001, you have the right to access, to interfere with the data, the right not to be subject to an individual decision and the right to appeal to the court. At the same time, you have the right to oppose the processing of your personal data and request the deletion of the data *. For the exercise of these rights, you may address us with a written, dated and signed application sent electronically by using our Contact page. You are also granted the right to appeal to the courts. If any of your data is incorrect, please inform us as soon as possible. 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order and sometimes when you vote for a listed site or server for anti-cheat protection.  
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. When placing an order we will require your name and address. For European costumers that represent a company we may also require a valid Business name, Registration number and VAT before placing an order. When voting for a listed site or server we may collect your entered game user and IP address to prevent double-voting and also to validate your vote. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
• To prevent booting or any kind of ways to cheat the voting system  
• To process payments and transactions  
• At the point when an end-user wishes to make a payment, his registration details may be passed to Paypal that provides payment processing services, in order for Paypal to better protect service and end-users from unauthorized payments. 

> Your information, whether public or private, will NOT be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To send email notifications and reminders when your advertising service may expire

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. Special situations may require disclosure of your data.

**Do we use cookies?**

**Google will show only non-personalized ads to all users in the EEA.**   
We use cookies only to save your login preferences for future visits and to prevent booting and voting cheats. Once you register, login or you access the voting page for any of the listed sites or servers you agree to our privacy policy. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.   
Our website uses a third party protection service offered by Cloudflare. This service may place cookies on the browsers in order to track malicious visitors, to reduce the chance of blocking legitimate users, and to provide customized services. The __cfduid cookie by Cloudflare is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from. If you do not want CloudFlare to use cookies, you can disable them within your browser. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using and accessing topg.org website, you consent to our privacy policy.

Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, notification or text.   
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please  __Contact Us  
Last updated on May 26, 2018
